# JACK MONRO

CONTACT
07444 485086
Jacknickm13@gmail.com
Hungerford, Berkshire
SKILLS
Chef
Cleaner
Builder
Warehouse Lead
EDUCATION
Las Vegas Academy of the Arts
2015-2018
LANGUAGES
English •
Polish

#### PROFILE

My name is Jack Monro, I have worked in many fields and have enjoyed and excelled in each one. I take my employment seriously and go above and beyond to make sure the job given to me is done to perfection. I am punctual and efficient. I keep a clean workspace and greet customers with a smile. I have a passion for visual arts and travel and I think that I bring this focus to detail into everything that I approach. I am a dedicated employee and place my focus on customer satisfaction and take great pleasure in knowing that my customers leave feeling satisfied and welcomed

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Travel

11-2022 - 10-23

I traveled for a year all across the United Sates and Europe. Spent lots of time learning new cultures and languages. I specifically spent a lot of time in Poland traveling all over and working on my understanding of the Polish language.

#### Warehouse Lead, QLI International

09-2021 - 11-2022

Responsibilities and Achievements

Managed inventory and staff in an 85,000 ft. warehouse for the renovation of the Beau Rivage, which is a 1,700 room hotel in Biloxi, Mississippi. I prepared weekly reports to the client, MGM Casinos, concerning inventory and damages.

# Deinstallation Supervisor, Buddy's Home Furnishings

02-2022 - 06-2022

Responsibilities and Achievements

I trained and managed a team to deinstall furniture and art during renovations at the Beau Rivage hotel in Biloxi, Mississippi.

#### Kitchen Porter, Cobbs Farm Shop & Kitchen

01/2020 - 05/2020

Responsibilities and Achievements

Starting as a KP, I gained experience working in a fast paced environment. I worked collaboratively with front of house and the kitchen to ensure that every task was completed to the best of my abilities and in a timely manner. Shortly after showing my work ethic and ability to take on new challenges I was promoted to assistant chef.

### Server, Las Vegas Rescue Mission

01/2018 - 12/2018

Responsibilities & Achievements

Prepared and served meals for underprivileged and often overlooked members of society. Provided a service role ensuring customers were satisfied, often going the extra mile to make sure that our patrons left happy and well looked after.

# Staff, Pieology

10/2017 - 10/2018

Responsibilities & Achievements

Prepared customized pizzas for our guests, making sure that all pizzas were fresh and full of flavour. I always made sure that the quality of the product leaving the kitchen was the highest standard it could be, always striving for a hygienic workplace.

# Builder, Tommy's House Flippers

04/2016 - 05/2018

Responsibilities & Achievements

All necessary work from plumbing to electrical, fixing up old houses in Las Vegas to modern permanent residences.

#### Cleaner, Freelance

01/2016 - 09/2018

Responsibilities & Achievements

Cleaned houses around the Las Vegas, Clark County area, paying specific attention to customer satisfaction and thorough property cleaning. I worked hard to ensure every property I left was presentable, and that my clients were happy